e883d4e|chore: verify and finalize migration
fe7a3fe|feat: implement main application pages
91f6097|feat: add api route handlers
ef593ab|feat: add trpc routers for ai operations
2350a8e|feat: implement background jobs with inngest
ccdb555|feat: update database schema for ai providers
d28979f|chore: update dependencies and project config
596af72|Merge pull request #4 from BMK-331/background-jobs
b75faf6|Merge branch 'main' into background-jobs
cee748a|Merge pull request #3 from BMK-331/Theme-Styling
a16ed35|ui: update global styles and home page
4f943b9|feat: add auth layout and provider icons
4cad83b|feat: add inngest client and route handler
ff106ea|feat: add workflow procedures to trpc
fb913d8|feat: add workflow schema to prisma
fddda67|chore: add mprocs config
f28059c|chore: add inngest dependencies
2bcb9e2|ui: update auth page wrappers to use new layout
da4fa12|ui: enhance auth forms with brand icons and styles
1383175|ui: add authentication layout structure
